Would you expect or demand a Harry Potter quiz?
I would demand it.
Here we go.
I also, we went to go and see the Harry Potter play the other day.
Oh yeah, yeah.
And I've been avoiding it because I just didn't really get it.
I was like, a Harry Potter play?
A play?
Really?
It's amazing.
Platform nine and three quarters.
Best to do it at a run, if you're nice.
Mischief managed.
albus is missing i need to find my son we need to there it is
have you seen it i've not i'm still holding out the day when i want
to do it both over a weekend oh see we did it on the same
day ah yeah that's a lot of potter but it it doesn't feel like a
lot of potter the show is so captivating the story is incredible and then you
go for lunch in the middle you have a nice lunch it's a long day
yeah but it's amazing all right let's crack through these okay in quidditch how many
points is it worth if you score with a quaffle 25 points i think it's
10 oh yeah
Angelina Johnson scores!
Ten points for Gryffindor.
It's not going well, Tom.
I got told off for making the first questions in the first round too easy.
Too easy, OK, OK, damn.
In Harry Potter and the Philosophers Not Sorcerer's Stone, what is the spell that Hermione
casts on the Hogwarts Express when she first meets Harry?
Oculus Reparo.
Oh, my God, so good.
What is the name of the fantastic beast, or let's say magical creature, that you
can see if you've witnessed and come to terms with death.
It's that horsey thing.
And it is called...
An oracle.
Begins with a T.
A...
at this old school that's true a sister all a festival there it is festival
that's how she sounds what are they we don't have time to go through the
seven Horcruxes I'm just gonna trust you it's easy yeah yeah at what train station
does Dumbledore meet Harry at the start of half-blood prince servicen train station take my
arm bloody hell do as i say bloody hell okay what is the
name of the muggles studies professor at hogwarts played by carolyn pickles in deathly hell
is part one is that the poor lady that gets killed ah this was in
a pub quiz the other day and we didn't get it right oh i'm having
flashbacks okay a first name is something really really nice something you might do for
people that's really pleasant nice thing for the world you've got one of your own
with your brother
a charity davies what is it i don't know i don't
know such a swing charity burbage yeah i yeah i didn't know that I didn't
know that to those of you who do not know we are joined tonight by
Miss Charity Burbage who until recently taught at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry
thanks for watching if you enjoyed this video don't forget to subscribe and click the
bell icon to keep up to date you can listen to my radio on movies
and tv podcast screen time on BBC sounds and you can find these interviews in
full on BBC iPlayer by searching movies with Ali Plum
you